

CONTACT



yesimhozman@gmail.com



<u>my portfolio</u>





ABOUT ME

I was formerly a mathematics teacher, and my passion for technology got me here. I worked with international teams with agile methodologies.

I am curious about new ideas and projects all the time. I can describe myself as a lifelong learner.

BOOTCAMPS

• Front-End Foxes (09.22-10.22)

Working with developers all around the world and developing projects and contributing open-sources with the

• Re-Coded (04.2021-09.2021)

I got a scholarship from Re:Coded and The Deutsche Gesellschaft für Internationale Zusammenarbeit (GIZ) GmbH and started a front-end development bootcamp from Flatiron School.

EDUCATION

Bogaziçi University

Educational Technology Master's Program 10/2020-06/2023 GPA: 3.65

Flatiron School

Front-End Development Bootcamp 04/2021-09/2021

Bogaziçi University

Department of Mathematics Education BA Degree 2015-2020 GPA: 3.01

Yeşim Akar Hozman

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front End Developer

Next-Gen Solution & Innovation 07/2021-10/2022 I created and managed e-commerce websites using Twig, Scss, and Javascript. Responsive websites are created by using React and Vue frameworks.

- Experience building Shopware e-commerce backends
- Developing themes and managing plugins on Shopware 6
- Using Twig, Scss, Bootstrap, Javascript & jQuery to develop e-commerce websites.
- Using Git for version control.
- Knowledge of UX/UI Design Principles.
- Experience working in a scrum process.
- Experience in agile project management.
- Experience in different component libraries (MaterialUI, React Bootstrap, React Router)

Curriculum Developer for Coding Classes

Boğaziçi University Educational Technology Research Center & Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality 09/2021-05/2022

I was a part of the curriculum development team. We design coding lesson plans for K-12 students. Experience with working in collaboration.

Volunteer Project Member

EKIP Social Cooperative Project 03/2020-08/2020 I worked on an EU project. It helps me to improve my research skills to solve various problems.

Mathematics Teacher (2018-2020)

Working in three different schools in Istanbul. It helps me to improve my communication, time management, and creativity skills.

CERTIFICATES

- Front End Development Libraries/ FreeCodeCamp
- Boğaziçi University Fine Art Certificate 2020 (Sculpture)
- Certificate of Europass Erasmus+ Project -Spain